{
    "subject": "resource/Marion_Francis_Forst",
    "predicate": "property/church",
    "object": "resource/Roman_Catholic_Church",
    "human_readable": "Marion Francis Forst was a member of the Roman Catholic Church.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9455084800720215,
            "question": "What was the religious affiliation of Marion Francis Forst?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9437914490699768,
            "question": "What religion was Marion Francis Forst a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9041722416877747,
            "question": "To which religious institution did Marion Francis Forst belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8548747301101685,
            "question": "What church did Marion Francis Forst attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7845411896705627,
            "question": "Was Marion Francis Forst devout?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7398446798324585,
            "question": "In what faith was Marion Francis Forst raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.721369743347168,
            "question": "What denomination did Marion Francis Forst follow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7127359509468079,
            "question": "What religious beliefs did Marion Francis Forst hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7116575837135315,
            "question": "Was Marion Francis Forst associated with any specific faith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6973426938056946,
            "question": "Did Marion Francis Forst practice any religion?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marion Francis Forst was a member of the Roman Catholic Church.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3999_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Marion Francis Forst associated with any specific faith?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3999_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What religious beliefs did Marion Francis Forst hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3999_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What denomination did Marion Francis Forst follow?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3999_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3999_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3999_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3999_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3999_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3999_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3999_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3999_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3999_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3999_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3999_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple is \"Marion Francis Forst was a member of the Roman Catholic Church.\" \n\nBased on the provided context information, there are multiple documents that mention Marion Francis Forst's affiliation with the Roman Catholic Church. For example:\n\n- In document \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3999/re-ranker-msmarco/53.txt\", it is mentioned: \"The Most Rev.  Marion Francis Forst, a Roman Catholic bishop in Kansas for 47 years...\"\n\nThis indicates that Marion Francis Forst was indeed associated with the Roman Catholic Church.\n\nTherefore, the answer should be:\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Marion Francis Forst was a Roman Catholic bishop, which strongly supports the statement that he was a member of the Roman Catholic Church."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}